Phúc#Phúc means Happiness, is represented for luck and blissful life in East Asian culture. People hope that “Happiness” could bring to them a peace , prosperity in lunar new year
Lộc#Lộc means Fortune, is represented for luckiness. The “Fortune” is suitable for people who have their own business or who would like to get promotion in the new year.
Thọ#Thọ means Longevity, is a meaningful wishes for parents, grand parents from offspring, wish them live long and healthy. 
Nhẫn#Nhẫn means Patience - a reminder for people to keep calm to deal with any issue in life. 
Trí#Trí means Intelligence, is represented for wisdom and knowledge. 
Tâm#Heart is usually used to help people to think about goodness, to build up a good mind inside them, live positively and do more charities for others.
Thành#Thành means Success - a wish for a successful new year. 
Dũng#Dũng means Bravery - hope that we could go through everything bravely, fearlessly and enough conscious to decide rightly.
Tài#Tài means Talent - hope that we can promote talent to achieve success. 
An#An means Peace, is one of the most favorite calligraphy of Vietnamese to hang in their houses. Vietnamese hope that they will have a peaceful and happy life in the new year.
Mỹ#Mỹ means Flawless, is represented for beauty not only about the outside but also the inside.
Đức#Đức means Kindness is represented for dignity, beautiful soul of human. 